





AVINASH UI/UX Designer







UI/UX DESIGNER

As a passionate UI/UX designer, I specialize in creating intuitive and visually appealing digital experiences. With a keen eye for detail and a deep understanding of user-centered design principles, I strive to craft interfaces that not only delight users but also meet their evolving needs effectively.

SKILLS

User Research Wireframing and Prototyping

Visual Design

Interaction Design Information Architecture

Accessibility

Problem Solving

Collaboration and Communication

Front-end development

TOOLS & FRAMEWORK

• Figma

Sketch

Photoshop

React JS

Adobe XD

UX PIN

Illustrator

Tailwind CSS

Mockflow

Zeplin

Spline 3D

Bootstrap

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Arizon Digital Apr 2024 - May 2024

Product Analyst

Designed a SAAS Application Conducted UI/UX Evaluation

Team Lead

Product Analysis and Solution

Reported directly to CEO

Freelancer Apr 2019 - Mar 2024

Audio Engineer

As a freelancing audio engineering student, I assisted Composers in planning and executing various projects, ensuring adherence to project timelines and deliverables. Supervised by award winning Engineers and top industry professional.

Mar 2013 - Mar 2019 **Brainobrain Pvt Itd**

UI/UX Designer

Principle Product Designer

Conducted User research with user's from more than 20 Countries

Implemented Management system for effective work-flow within the organisation

Graphic Design

Brand Identity Design

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Commerce

Majors: Accounts Commerce and Economics Annamalai University - 2015

PGDM in Human Resources Management

Annamalai University - 2017

Diploma in Sound Engineering

The Audiophile School of Sound Engineering - 2023

CERTIFICATIONS

Foundations of UX

HIGH FIDEL PROTOTYPING

USER INTERFACE DESIGN

WIREFRAMING

UX DESIGN

UX RESEARCH